Fried, John H. E.; Papers ger014
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- General correspondence, 1938-1990; 7; 319 file folders
  - Correspondence with publishers, 7.505 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 19-58)
    - The University of Michigan Press (Fred D. Wieck), 1958-1960 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 56)
    - War Department, 1942 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 57)
    - Washington Post, 1949 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 57)
    - WIN Magazine, 1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 57)
    - Worldmark Press (Moshe Sachs), 1958-1961 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Correspondence with organizations, institutions, 7.506
    - American Association for the United Nations (A.A.U.N.), Manhattan Chapter, Undated (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 59)
      membership lists, letterhead.
    - A.A.U.N. Speakers Bureau, 1944-1961 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 60)
    - A.A.U.N., 1956-1962 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 61)
    - A.A.U.N. - Eleanor Roosevelt letters, 1956-1958 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 62)
    - Ad Hoc Committee for Panama, 1990 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 63)
    - Agenda for Non-Collaboration, 1983 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 63)
    - American Association of Former Austrian Jurists, 1946 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 63)
    - American Association of University Professors (AAUP), 1958 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 63)
    - American Civil Liberties Union (Charles Morgan Jr), 1967 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 63)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1952 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 63)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1966 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 64)
    - American Political Science Association, 1958-1970 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 65)
    - The American Society for the Study of the German Democratic Republic, 1975 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 66)
    - The American Society for International Law, 1965-1987 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 66)
    - American Veterans Committee, 1967-1968 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
    - Amnesty International, 1975 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
    - Arms Control Association, 1977 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 67)
    - Association Internationale des Juristes Démocrates (A.I.J.D.; Joë Nordman, Nicole Gerard), 1978-1990 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 68)
    - B'nai B'rith Youth Organization, 1961 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 69)
    - British Peace Assembly (Gordon Schaffer), 1985-1988 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 69)
    - Brookline Public Schools, 1979 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 70)
    - Bundesministerium der Justiz, Bonn, Undated (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 70)
    - Campaign for UN Reform (Walter Hoffmann), 1980 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 71)
    - Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1954-1958 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
    - The Catholic Worker, 1955 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
    - Center for Constitutional Rights (Michael Ratner), 1986 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
    - Center for Defense Information, 1977-1981 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
    - Center for the Study of the Causes of War and Conditions of Peace, Utah State University, 1967-1968 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
    - Center for War/Peace Studies (Richard Hudson), 1980 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 72)
    - Center on Law and Pacifisim (William R. Durland), 1978-1981 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 73)
    - Central Intelligence Agency, 1975 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 74)
    - Centre de Documentation Juive Contemporaine, 1951 (Box 8 (7-General correspondence), Folder 75)
    - The Club of Rome, 1979; 1987 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 1)
    - Coalition for a New Foreign and Military Policy, 1977-1980 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 1)
    - Collegiate Council for the United Nations, 1960-1961 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Comité International de la Croix-Rouge (International Red Cross; Bruno Zimmermann), 1987-1988 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Commission of the Churches on International Affairs, 1955 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Committee for Effective Use of the International Court, 1961 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
    - The Committee for World Development and World Disarmament, 1958 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 2)
    - Common Cause, 1982 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 3)
    - Consultative Council of Jewish Organizations (Moses Moskowitz), 1955-1957 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
    - COPRED (Consortium on Peace Research, Education and Development), 1976-1982 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Cornerstone, 1980 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 4)
    - Council for a Livable World, 1964-1987 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 5)
    - Council for Democracy, Undated (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Council on Intercultural Relations, 1942 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Council on Religion and International Affairs (A. William Loos), 1970-1978 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 6)
    - Department of State, 1961-1978 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 7)
    - Emergency Committee in Aid of Displaced Foreign Scholars, 1946 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists, 1947 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 8)
    - Federation of American Scientists (F.A.S., Jeremy J. Stone), 1975-1981 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 9)
    - The Fellowship of Reconciliation (James Forest), 1971-1977 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 10)
    - The Field Foundation, Inc., 1945 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 11)
    - Ford Foundation, 1954-1956 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 11)
    - The Foundation for Freedom & Democracy in Community Life (Donald S. Frey), 1973-1974 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 11)
    - Foundation for the Establishment of an International Criminal Court (F.E.I.C.C.) - Correspondence with Robert K. Woetzel, 1966-1979 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 12)
    - F.E.I.C.C. - Woetzel, Robert, 1980-1990 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 13)
    - F.E.I.C.C. - general correspondence, 1973-1990 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 14)
    - F.E.I.C.C. - IVth International Criminal Law Conference (Caribbean Seminar, San Juan Puerto Rico), 1976 January 09-1976 January 13 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 15)
    - F.E.I.C.C. - NGO Conference on "What Future for South Africa?" (UN Headquarters), 1977 June 22 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 16)
    - F.E.I.C.C. - miscellaneous materials, Undated (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 17)
    - Fort Hood Three Defense Committee, 1966 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
    - Friends Committee on National Legislation, 1982 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 18)
    - The Fund for Peace (Stewart Rawlings Mott), 1981-1982 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 19)
    - Hudson Institute, 1963 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Indian Society of International Law, 1964-1970 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Institute for International Order (L. Larry Leonard), 1960 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 20)
    - Institute for Policy Studies (Ralph Stavins), 1976 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 21)
    - Institute for the Study of Genocide, 1983-1988 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 21)
    - International Association of Democratic Lawyers, 1982 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 21)
    - International Association of Lawyers Against Nuclear Arms (IALANA), 1987-1989 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 22)
    - International Atomic Energy Agency, 1957-1958 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 23)
    - International Bank for Reconstruction and Development, 1954 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 23)
    - International Institute for the Unification of Private Law, 1955 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 23)
    - International Institute of Social Research, Columbia, 1938-1939 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 23)
    - International Law Association (I.L.A.), general correspondence, 1958-1978 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 24)
    - I.L.A. Committee on Armed Conflict (Alfred P. Rubin), 1980-1984 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 25)
    - I.L.A. Committee on International Terrorism (John F. Murphy), 1984-1986 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 26)
    - I.L.A. Committee on the Charter of the United Nations, 1972 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 27)
    - I.L.A. Human Rights Committee (Richard B. Lillich), 1977-1984 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 28)
    - International Law Commission (Alexander Yankov), 1986 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
    - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War, Undated (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
    - International Progress Organization (I.P.O., Hans Köchler), 1989 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 29)
    - International Psychohistorical Association, 1978 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
    - International Society for military law and law of war, 1971-1972 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
    - International Studies Association (Richard B. Finnegan), 1980 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 30)
    - John Simon Guggenheim Foundation, 1951-1964 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 31)
    - Law and Society Association, 1974 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
    - Lawyers Alliance for Nuclear Arms Control, 1982-1986 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
    - Lawyers for Nuclear Disarmament (Owen Davies), 1983 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 32)
    - Medical Research Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
    - Meiklejohn Civil Liberties Institute, 1984-1989 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
    - Methodist Federation for Social Action (Lee H. Ball), 1982 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
    - Minority Rights Group, 1974 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 33)
    - Missouri Commission on Human Rights, 1959 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 34)
    - Mobilization for Survival, 1977-1981 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 35)
    - National Lawyers Guild, 1969 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 35)
    - National Refugee Service, 1938-1943 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 36)
    - NJ Fellowship for the Aged, 1972 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - New York City Committee for the 25th Anniversary of the United Nations, 1970 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - New York Society for Ethical Culture, 1977 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Office of the High Commissioner for Refugees, 1951-1954 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Office of War Information (OWI), 1945 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 37)
    - Peace Research Institute - Dundas, 1979 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 38)
    - Pershing Plowshares Support Committee, 1984 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 38)
    - Physicians for Social Responsibility, 1963-1983 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 38)
    - Promoting Enduring Peace, 1963-1989 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 38)
    - Rockefeller Foundation, 1940-1963 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1976 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Social Science Research Council, 1946-1962 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 39)
    - Social Scientists Against Nuclear War, 1982 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Society for the Prevention of World War III, Inc., 1954 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Spanish Refugee Aid, Inc. (Nancy Macdonald), 1976-1988 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - Swords Into Ploughshares, London, 1990 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 40)
    - UNESCO, 1973 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 41)
    - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1978-1983 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 41)
    - United World Federalists, Incorporated, 1949 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 41)
    - Vereinigung der Juristen der Deutschen Demokratischen Republik, 1987 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 42)
    - War Resisters' International, 1968 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
    - War Resisters League, 1977 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
    - World Committee for a World Constitutional Convention, 1971 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
    - World Constitution & Parliament Association, Inc., 1972 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 43)
    - World Federalists Association, 1977-1981 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
    - World Jewish Congress, 1951 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
    - World Peace Through Law Center, 1972-1977 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
    - World Peace University, 1986 (Box 9 (7-General correspondence), Folder 44)
- Teaching materials, 1940-1976; 8; 108 file folders
  This series consists primarily of course notes and outlines, and also contains correspondence with administration and other faculty members, student papers and evaluations.
  - City College of the City of New York, 1940-1942; 8.1 (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 45-54)
    - Personnel file, 1940-1943 (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 45)
    - British Constitutional Developments. Course notes, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 46)
    - Comparative Government. Course notes, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 47)
    - Government. Course notes, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 48)
    - France. Course notes, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 49)
    - Great Britain and British Dominions. Course notes, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 50)
    - International Relations. Course notes, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 51)
    - Political Theories. Course notes, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 52)
    - Reading lists, bibliographies, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 53)
    - Students, Undated (Box 9 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 54)
  - Columbia University, 1941-1951; 8.2 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 1-5)
    - Correspondence, 1941-1942 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 1)
    - Comparative Labor Problems. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 2)
    - Student papers, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 3)
    - "Balkan Area Social Legislation". Columbia University lecture, 1944 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 4)
    - Columbia University, War Documentation Project, 1951 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 5)
  - New School for Social Research Seminar: "The Basic Construction: War in an Era of Pacifism", 1942 January 07 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 6)
  - City College of the City University of New York, 1949-1950; 8.4 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 7-11)
    - Personnel file, 1949-1950 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 7)
    - U.S. Department of State Intern Program, 1950 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 8)
    - Comparative Government. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 9)
    - Government. Course outlines, notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 10)
    - World Politics. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 11)
  - New School for Social Research, 1954-1965; 8.5 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 12-26)
    - Personnel records, 1954-1964 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 12)
    - Ascoli, Max. Correspondence, 1940 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 13)
    - Colm, Gerhart. Correspondence, 1940 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 14)
    - Hula, Erich. Correspondence, 1940; 1954 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 15)
    - Johnson, Alvin. Correspondence, 1942; 1958 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 16)
    - Lowe, Adolph. Correspondence, 1949 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 17)
    - Padover, Saul K. Correspondence, 1958; 1977 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 18)
    - Simons, Hans. Correspondence, 1941-1955 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 19)
    - Speier, Hans. Correspondence, 1940-1954 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 20)
    - Staudinger, Hans. Correspondence, 1943-1962 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 21)
    - Todd, Elizabeth. Correspondence, 1954 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 22)
    - New School Bulletin. Course listings, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 23)
    - Course outlines (proposed), Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 24)
    - International Law. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 25)
    - Study outlines, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 26)
  - City University of New York, 1954-1962; 8.6 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 27-60)
    - Students, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 27)
    - Personnel file, 1954-1962 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 28)
    - Comparative Political and Economic Systems. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 29)
    - Defense, War and Disarmament. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 30)
    - Elements of Political Philosophy. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 31)
    - Elements of Politics. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 32)
    - Ideas that Changed the World. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 33)
    - International Law. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 34)
    - Issues and Trends in World Affairs. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 35)
    - Understanding World Problems. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 36)
    - War, Armament and Disarmament in the Nuclear Age. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 37)
    - The Western Heritage of Political Thought. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 38)
    - Study: "Hitler's Rise Through Intimidation and Denunciation", 1954 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 39)
    - Study: "Political Thought in Post-Hitler Germany", 1954 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 40)
    - Summer School in Scandinavia, 1957 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 41)
    - Study: "Rights of Refugees", 1954-1955 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 42)
    - Study: "Factors and Attitude influencing the Conduct of Foreign Policy", 1956 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 43)
    - General Studies, 1955-1963 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 44)
    - School of Commerce, 1957-1958 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 45)
    - Graduate School of Business Administration, 1958-1960 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 46)
    - Study: "Economic Regionalism in Europe", 1960 October 26 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 47)
    - Graduate School of Public Administration, 1961-1962 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 48)
    - Administrative Problems of Developing Countries. Course notes, 1962 Spring (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 49)
    - Comparative Economic Systems and Public Administration. Course notes, 1963 Spring (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 50)
    - Economic Theory. Course notes, 1958-1960 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 51)
    - European Democracies in Transition. Course notes, 1962 Spring (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 52)
    - Foreign Trade. Course notes, 1958 Summer (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 53)
    - Framework of International Business. Course notes, 1963 Spring (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 54)
    - International Business. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 55)
    - Islam. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 56)
    - Political theory. Course notes, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 57)
    - Students, 1955-1978 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 58)
    - Student papers, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 59)
    - Bryce, Avis. Thesis, 1961-1962 (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 60)
  - Fairleigh Dickinson University, 1958 Spring (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 61)
  - Long Island University, 1959 Spring-1961 Summer (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 62)
    Correspondence.
  - Long Island University. Course notes: Contemporary U.S. Foreign Policy, Undated (Box 10 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 63)
  - Queens College, 1959 Spring (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 1)
  - State University of New York, Albany, 1961 Spring (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 2)
  - State University of New York, New Paltz, 1961 (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 3)
  - State University of New York, New Paltz. Student papers, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 4)
  - University of Pittsburgh, 1963 Winter (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 5)
  - City College, 1963 Summer (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 6)
  - Lehmann College, City University of New York, 1965-1976; 8.16 (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 7-29)
    - Personnel records, 1965-1976 (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 7)
    - Tenure proceedings, 1970-1971 (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 8)
    - New York University Bulletins of course listings, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 9)
    - Armstrong, Anne. Correspondence, 1978-1980 (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 10)
    - Bosworth, William A., 1970-1978 (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 11)
    - Lief, Leonard, 1967-1982 (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 12)
    - Faculty correspondence, general, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 13)
    - American Foreign Policy. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 14)
    - Current International Relations. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 15)
    - Democratic Theory - Phases and Problems. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 16)
    - German and Central European Political Systems. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 17)
    - International and Regional Organizations. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 18)
    - International Law. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 19)
    - International Politics. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 20)
    - Principles and Problems of International Law. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 21)
    - The United Nations. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 22)
    - The U.S. in World Affairs. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 23)
    - War and the Prevention of War. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 24)
    - World Government. Course notes, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 25)
    - Lehmann College, general course outlines, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 26)
    - Sabbatical report, Undated (Box 11 (8-Teaching materials), Folder 27)